ADITTIA AGUSTIAN

+628990364658 | agustianaa12adit@gmail.com | Linkedin Me | Karawang, Indonesia

SELF DESCRIPTION



I graduated from the Bachelor of Information Systems at Buana Perjuangan University Karawang, I have experience in the field of IT web development and Full Stack Developer, previously I had several internships related to web development and web creation, most recently I interned at PERUM PERURI for 1 year in the PMMB and MAGENTA BUMN programs.

EXPERIENCE

Karawang Library 12/11/2019 – 15/05/2020

Building a Karawang Library Web System (Research and Internship)

- Design and design library web systems.
- Collaborate with the team to build a library web system.

LP3M Buana Perjuangan University Karawang LP3M E-Cycle Web Development (Internship)

15/06/2020 - 14/05/2021

- Collaborate with the team to develop the E-Cycle web.
- Improved features and improvements in the e-cycle web system.
- Make data designs, and programmers in developing e-cycle web.

Covid-19 Vaccine IT Team Services and IT Support (Internship)

02/06/2021 - 15/02/2022

- Collaborate with the team in conducting Covid-19 Vaccine IT services.
- Increasing the input of data on Covid-19 cases in Karawang Regency.
- IT Support in Vaccine and Covid-19 activities.

PERUM PERURI 19/09/2022 - 28/02/2023

Full Stack Web Developer (Internship)

- Employee services, to serve the needs of each employee such as submitting evidence of reimbursement of costs, applying for doctor's leave, applying for leave permits, submitting active work certificates, PAKLARING, etc.
- Make a letter of guarantee for the manufacture of glasses.
- Create a web system for employee facilities.
- Creating Perum PERURI Employee Recreation Assistance System.
- Create an employee data web system for each subsidiary of Perum Peruri.

PERUM PERURI 1/03/2023 - 31/08/2023

Web Development (Internship)

- Development of the Employee Facility system.
- Development of the PERUM PERURI employee recreation assistance system.
- Develop a web-based cost monitoring information system that aims to streamline the cost tracking process.
- Configure the server to implement the web system by making the necessary configurations on the XAMPP, SSH, and server IP settings.

PERUM PERURI 15/09/2023 – Present

Web Development (Operational Human Resources (HR)) (Contract)

 Development of a web-based remuneration system for recreation assistance and addition of features for POH (Daily Operational Holder) data management.

- Creating a web-based digital counter system, named smart-counter.
- Planning application projects.
- Creating document workflows within the application project.
- Developing a functioning web application.
- Drafting documents such as spectacle guarantee letters, dental guarantee letters, and others.
- Assisting in the internship recruitment process for the MAGENTA BUMN program at PERUM PERURI.
- Conducting user interviews and providing information to every prospective intern.
- Assisting in the distribution of PERUM PERURI's uniforms.
- Participating in all activities of the HR Division.
- Operating vmix broadcast during every event.
- Managing servers in the Operational HR Department.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Systems, Faculty of Computer Science Buana Perjuangan University, Karawang

2019 - 2023

Current Cumulative GPA: 3.93/4.00 Click to view

ABILITY

Information System: Web Development, Database, User Experience, UML

• Programming language: PHP, Javascript, Python, SQL, MySQL

Front End: CSS, HTML, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap and ReactJS

• Web Framework: Codeigniter Framework, Laravel Framework

Design: CorelDraw, Figma, Photoshop

Broadcast : Vmix, OBS

Hard Skill: Web Development, Full Stack Developer, Data Science, Design, Configuration Server

Soft Skill: Team Work, Adaptability, Attention to Detail, Collaboration, Problem Solving

• Tools used: Visual Studio Code, UML, XAMPP, MySQL WorkBench, Postman, Google Colab

PROJECTS / PORTFOLIO

My Project Portfolio: My Portfolio

CERTIFICATE

- Web Development Group Competition (Sriwijaya University): Click to View
- Training on Making Music Listening Application (Coding.id): <u>Click to View</u>
- Create Email Blast with Python (Coding.id): <u>Click to View</u>
- Basic Git Command Training (Coding.id): Click to View
- SQL Fundamental Course Training (Sololearn): <u>Click to View</u>
- React + Redux Course Training (Sololearn): <u>Click to View</u>
- Covid-19 Volunteer Charter and Vaccination Kab. Karawang: Click to View
- BNSP Certification Web Development : <u>Click to View</u>
- Certified Student Internship Program (BUMN Perum Peruri): <u>Click to View</u>
- Talent Generation Internship Program (MAGENTA): Click to View
- Laravel 9 basic training (Binary Campus): Click to View